CARMEN GOETZ

224 Lakeridge Drive, Warman, SK, S0K 0A1 | (306) 880-4773 | carmen.b.goetz@gmail.com

OBJECTIVE

Looking for Job opportunities in Web Development to utilize my training in Computer Systems Technology at SaskPolytech and build my career.

SKILLS & ABILITIES

I have experience with programming languages HTML, CSS, JavaScript, JQuery, JSON, PHP, MySQL, Java, C#, C, Xamarin and more.

I received training in Microsoft Word, Excel, Access, SharePoint, and PowerPoint and utilized these programs regularly.

I utilize test-driven programming, and agile software development

I work independently and with a team and can work well in both types of environments.

I am able to work with Windows, Linux, and MacOS operating systems.

I have received education in computer networking, security, and hardware.

EDUCATION

Computer Systems Technology Diploma,

Saskatoon, Saskatchewan Polytechnic

August 2016 - Present

Medical Terminology, Professional Practices, and Infection Control & Safety,

Saskatoon, Saskatchewan Polytechnic

January 2012 – May 2012

High School Diploma with Honors,

Saskatoon, Evan Hardy Collegiate

2007 - 2011

CARMEN GOETZ

Warman, SK | (306) 880-4773 | carmen.b.goetz@gmail.com

VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE

Facilitator, Canada Learning Code

· I ran a workshop for a Kids Learning Code workshop in Game making with Scratch. I gave a presentation, with examples and exercises, and helped the children learn how to use Scratch and understand basic programming functions.

Mentor, Canada Learning Code

• Supported up to 4 learners, adults and children, throughout a day long workshop. I was responsible for answering questions they had, and helped them working through exercises. I have mentored HTML & CSS.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Sales and Service Representative, SaskTel

June 2013 - Present

- · Working in a large call centre in a fast-paced sales department
- · Meeting and exceeding quarterly sales targets
- · Navigating complex computer programs
- · Implementing first call resolution

Sales Associate, Gap Factory

November 2012 - January 2015

- · Worked as a team in a diverse environment
- · Assisted customers with their needs

Front Cashier, The Strawberry Ranch

July 2012 - September 2012

- · Worked independently while answering calls, and helping customers
- · Prepared produce for sale, and filled customer orders

Cashier, Dutch Growers

April 2012 - June 2012

CARMEN GOETZ

Warman, SK | (306) 880-4773 | carmen.b.goetz@gmail.com

REFERENCES

References available upon request.